=His Chosen Favor=
=مفضلته المختارة=
(Xiao Wenjing, have you considered making bombs?)
(شياو وينجينغ، هل فكرتِ في صنع قنابل؟)
=Episode 6=
=الحلقة 6=
(Empress Regnant Lu Zhen'er)
(الإمبراطورة الحاكمة لو تشن إر)
Consort Lu saved His Majesty,
أنقذت الزوجة لو جلالته،
so specially rewarded with 100,000 taels of gold,
لذلك تمت مكافأته بشكل خاص بمبلغ 100,000 تيل من الذهب،
100 bolts of silk,
100 لفة من الحرير،
ten Southern luminous pearls,
عشر لآلئ جنوبية متلألئة،
two pairs of gold buyao hairpins,
زوجان من دبابيس الشعر الذهبية من نوع بوياو،
ten pairs of gold earrings,
عشرة أزواج من الأقراط الذهبية،
one pure gold longevity lock,
قفل ذهبي خالص واحد لإطالة العمر،
and a box of Dongzhu pearls.
وعلبة من لآلئ دونغتشو.
Tone it down.
خفف من حدة الأمر.
Your eyes are practically glued to these gold ornaments.
تكاد عيناك تلتصقان بهذه الحلي الذهبية.
Do they look good?
هل تبدو جيدة؟
Yes.
نعم.
Fu An, you may leave us now.
فو آن، يمكنك مغادرتنا الآن.
Who sent those assassins?
من أرسل هؤلاء القتلة؟
Have you found anything?
هل وجدت أي شيء؟
They're all dead.
لقد ماتوا جميعاً.
No survivors.
لا ناجين.
I suspect
أظن
it was likely Prince Rui.
من المرجح أنه كان الأمير روي.
I think so too.
أعتقد ذلك أيضاً.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Once I've recovered,
بمجرد أن أتعافى،
I'll test him out.
سأختبره.
I don't buy the plot nonsense.
لا أصدق هذه الحبكة السخيفة.
Recent events
الأحداث الأخيرة
are mostly man-made.
معظمها من صنع الإنسان.
Plus,
زائد،
we don't know the relationship
لا نعرف طبيعة العلاقة
between the original owner and Prince Rui.
بين المالك الأصلي والأمير روي.
He's definitely involved.
هو متورط بالتأكيد.
After you recover,
بعد تعافيك،
let me take you out.
دعني آخذك في نزهة.
Sounds great!
يبدو رائعاً!
Where to?
إلى أين؟
Have a beach barbecue.
أقم حفلة شواء على الشاطئ.
Yes! Perfect!
نعم! ممتاز!
Haven't been to the beach
لم أذهب إلى الشاطئ
in ages.
في العصور.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Xiao Wenjing,
شياو ون جينغ
why does this beach look so familiar?
لماذا يبدو هذا الشاطئ مألوفاً جداً؟
All beaches look pretty much the same.
تبدو جميع الشواطئ متشابهة إلى حد كبير.
Grilling meat and drinking beer by the sea
شواء اللحم وشرب البيرة على شاطئ البحر
is pure bliss.
إنها سعادة خالصة.
What are you smiling at?
ما الذي يجعلك تبتسم؟
There's something
هناك شيء ما
I'm not sure if I should tell you.
لست متأكدًا مما إذا كان ينبغي عليّ إخبارك.
What?
ماذا؟
This.
هذا.
(Empress Regnant Lu Zhen'er)
(الإمبراطورة الحاكمة لو تشن إر)
Where did you get this?
من أين حصلت على هذا؟
Under a shelf in your study.
تحت رف في مكتبك.
Come inside.
تفضل بالدخول.
Look!
ينظر!
A glowing peacock.
طاووس متوهج.
- It's so unique! - Keep your voice down.
- إنه فريد من نوعه! - اخفض صوتك.
What books do you want?
ما هي الكتب التي تريدها؟
All of...
كل...
What is this?
ما هذا؟
(Empress Regnant Lu Zhen'er)
(الإمبراطورة الحاكمة لو تشن إر)
(Empress Regnant? I'm actually going to be empress?)
(إمبراطورة حاكمة؟ هل سأصبح إمبراطورة فعلاً؟)
If that's the case,
إذا كان الأمر كذلك،
then I must be the heroine.
إذن لا بد أنني البطلة.
Are you that sure you're the heroine?
هل أنتِ متأكدة تماماً من أنكِ البطلة؟
Absolutely!
قطعاً!
I'll be Empress Regnant.
سأكون الإمبراطورة الحاكمة.
Doesn't it mean I'm the heroine?
ألا يعني ذلك أنني البطلة؟
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدًا،
I officially have the heroine aura.
أصبحتُ رسمياً أمتلك هالة البطلة.
Prince Rui? Empress Dowager Chen?
الأمير روي؟ الإمبراطورة الأرملة تشين؟
They're nothing!
إنهم لا شيء!
If you become Empress Regnant,
إذا أصبحتِ الإمبراطورة الحاكمة،
what about me?
ماذا عني؟
Does that mean I'll die?
هل هذا يعني أنني سأموت؟
Since I'm the heroine,
بما أنني البطلة،
you must be the hero.
يجب أن تكون أنت البطل.
In female-centric novels,
في الروايات التي تتمحور حول المرأة،
whoever the heroine chooses becomes hero.
من تختاره البطلة يصبح هو البطل.
No arguments.
لا جدال في ذلك.
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
Yes.
نعم.
But you said before
لكنك قلت من قبل
you'd defy fate.
ستتحدى القدر.
Life's easier with less meddling.
الحياة أسهل مع تدخل أقل.
♪When thunder roars♪
♪عندما يزمجر الرعد♪
Xiao Wenjing, have you considered
شياو وينجينغ، هل فكرتِ في
making bombs?
صنع القنابل؟
Bombs?
قنابل؟
As long as we succeed,
طالما أننا ننجح،
the military power of Beizhao
القوة العسكرية لمدينة بيتشاو
will skyrocket several levels.
سترتفع بشكل كبير إلى مستويات عديدة.
Not seeking fame in history books,
لا أسعى للشهرة في كتب التاريخ،
just aiming for global domination.
يهدف فقط إلى الهيمنة العالمية.
What?
ماذا؟
It just struck me
لقد خطرت لي هذه الفكرة فجأة
how perfectly you fit this role.
كم أنت مناسب تمامًا لهذا الدور.
I agree.
أنا موافق.
Rise.
يعلو.
Xiao Wenjing.
شياو ون جينغ.
Do you think after I become Empress Regnant,
هل تعتقدين أنه بعد أن أصبح الإمبراطورة الحاكمة،
I can start
يمكنني البدء
a harem?
حريم؟
Just imagining crowds of handsome men
مجرد تخيل حشود من الرجال الوسيمين
fighting over my favor
يتنافسون على كسب ودّي
makes me so happy!
هذا يسعدني كثيراً!
But I'll be benevolent.
لكنني سأكون كريماً.
Not only
ليس فقط
can palace maids leave at 25,
هل يمكن لخادمات القصر أن يغادرن في سن الخامسة والعشرين؟
male consorts over 25 can leave too.
يمكن للذكور المرافقين الذين تزيد أعمارهم عن 25 عامًا المغادرة أيضًا.
Thus,
هكذا،
my harem will always be filled
سيظل حريمي ممتلئًا دائمًا
with men in their early twenties.
مع رجال في أوائل العشرينات من عمرهم.
Why is it raining all of a sudden?
لماذا تمطر فجأة؟
You two reek of alcohol.
تفوح منكما رائحة الكحول.
Where have you been?
أين كنت؟
It's not late yet.
لم يفت الأوان بعد.
We were handling important matters.
كنا نتعامل مع أمور مهمة.
Prince Rui,
الأمير روي،
why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
I return to the palace whenever I please.
أعود إلى القصر متى شئت.
What's it to you?
وما شأنك أنت؟
Zhen'er, I told you
زين إير، لقد أخبرتك
Xiao Wenjing has treacherous ambitions.
لدى شياو وينجينغ طموحات غادرة.
He's no good.
إنه ليس جيداً.
How shameless of you
يا لك من وقح!
to sow discord between us
لزرع الفتنة بيننا
right to my face!
مباشرة في وجهي!
Xiao Wenjing,
شياو ون جينغ
dare you swear the assassination had nothing to do with you?
هل تجرؤ على أن تقسم أن عملية الاغتيال لا علاقة لك بها؟
What does he mean?
ماذا يقصد؟
Xiao Wenjing,
شياو ون جينغ
you don't dare.
لا تجرؤ.
Why wouldn't I dare?
لماذا لا أجرؤ؟
I swear right now!
أقسم بالله الآن!
If I had anything to do with the attempt,
لو كان لي أي دور في هذه المحاولة،
may my father
رحم الله والدي
never be reincarnated.
لن يتجسد مرة أخرى.
You unfilial wretch! What did you say?
يا لك من عاقّ! ماذا قلت؟
You asked me to swear,
طلبت مني أن أقسم،
and I swore it.
وأقسمت على ذلك.
Why are you angry?
لماذا أنت غاضب؟
Xiao Wenjing,
شياو ون جينغ
you're defying your elder.
أنت تتحدى من هو أكبر منك سناً.
You're being defying.
أنت تتحدى.
Xiao Yicheng,
شياو ييتشنغ,
don't think all that mansplaining
لا تظن أن كل هذا شرح ذكوري متعالٍ
makes you my father!
أنت تجعلني والدي!
How dare you,
كيف تجرؤ؟
a prince, speak to me like this?
أمير، يتحدث معي بهذه الطريقة؟
I'll exterminate your clan!
سأبيد عشيرتكم!
Were you shot in the head by a gun?
هل أصبت برصاصة في رأسك؟
A gun?
مسدس؟
What's a gun?
ما هو المسدس؟
- This
- هذا
- is a gun!
- إنها بندقية!
(Are they insane?)
(هل هم مجانين؟)
Xiao Wenjing,
شياو ون جينغ
how dare you!
كيف تجرؤ!
You hit me!
لقد ضربتني!
Stop fighting!
توقفوا عن القتال!
Stop it!
توقف عن ذلك!
I'll kill you!
سأقتلك!
That wench Lu Zhen'er
هذا الوغد لو Zhen'er
first seduced the late emperor.
أغوى الإمبراطور الراحل أولاً.
Now, she's bewitched Prince Rui
والآن، لقد سحرت الأمير روي
and Xiao Wenjing!
وشياو ونجينغ!
An emperor and a prince
إمبراطور وأمير
brawling in the palace! Unbelievable!
شجار في القصر! أمر لا يُصدق!
I will not allow her to live!
لن أسمح لها بالعيش!
Jingxi,
جينغشي,
come here.
تعال الى هنا.
Yes.
نعم.
Understood.
مفهوم.
I'll see to it immediately.
سأهتم بالأمر فوراً.
Lu Zhen'er,
لو زينير،
I'll not tolerate you!
لن أتحملك!
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
By Empress Dowager's decree,
بمرسوم من الإمبراطورة الأرملة،
I've come to purge the evil spirit.
لقد جئت لأطرد الروح الشريرة.
What evil spirit?
أي روح شريرة؟
All the koi in the imperial garden died.
ماتت جميع أسماك الكوي في الحديقة الإمبراطورية.
Empress Dowager dreams nightly of an evil spirit,
تحلم الإمبراطورة الأرملة كل ليلة بروح شريرة،
so Master Wu was summoned to perform rites.
لذلك تم استدعاء المعلم وو لأداء الطقوس.
He detected the spirit resides in Zhaohua Hall.
لقد اكتشف أن الروح تسكن في قاعة تشاوهوا.
I request your permission to search.
أطلب إذنكم لإجراء البحث.
Don't make this difficult for me.
لا تجعل الأمر صعباً عليّ.
Fine.
بخير.
Go ahead.
تفضل.
Tear the place apart.
دمروا المكان تدميراً.
If you find nothing,
إذا لم تجد شيئاً،
it'll prove my innocence.
سيثبت ذلك براءتي.
Good.
جيد.
Search it!
ابحث عنه!
Jingxi,
جينغشي,
I've found it!
لقد وجدتها!
You two.
أنتما الاثنان.
Please escort Consort Lu to Wanchun Hall.
يرجى مرافقة المحظية لو إلى قاعة وانشون.
Wait.
انتظر.
I can walk on my own.
أستطيع المشي بمفردي.
Stars of the Great Zenith, ceaselessly adapting.
نجوم الذروة العظيمة، تتكيف باستمرار.
Banish evil spirits, bind the demons, protect life, guard the body.
طرد الأرواح الشريرة، وتقييد الشياطين، وحماية الحياة، وحراسة الجسد.
Wisdom clear and bright, heart and mind tranquil.
حكمة صافية ومشرقة، وقلب وعقل هادئان.
Three souls eternal, seven spirits intact and steadfast.
ثلاثة أرواح أبدية، وسبعة أرواح سليمة وثابتة.
Empress Dowager,
الإمبراطورة الأرملة،
I found this
لقد وجدت هذا
in Consort Lu's palace.
في قصر كونسورت لو.
This is
هذا هو
a sorcery doll!
دمية سحرية!
Lu Zhen'er,
لو زينير،
you practice sorcery within the palace walls.
تمارس السحر داخل أسوار القصر.
You shall be punished.
ستُعاقب.
Guards!
حراس!
Drag this sorceress away.
اسحب هذه الساحرة بعيدًا.
Beat her to death immediately!
اضربها حتى الموت فوراً!
Empress Dowager,
الإمبراطورة الأرملة،
this is not sorcery.
هذا ليس سحراً.
It's merely a common
إنه مجرد أمر شائع
prayer doll!
دمية صلاة!
Master.
يتقن.
I accompany His Highness daily.
أرافق سموه يومياً.
Seeing him exhaust himself for Beizhao,
رؤيته وهو يبذل قصارى جهده من أجل بيتشاو،
my heart truly aches for him.
قلبي يتألم حقاً لأجله.
I suddenly recalled
تذكرت فجأة
a prayer method I heard of.
طريقة صلاة سمعت عنها.
As long as
طالما
I sincerely offer myself in exchange,
أعرض نفسي بكل صدق في المقابل،
I can protect those I wish to safeguard,
أستطيع حماية من أرغب في حمايتهم،
ensuring their peace and health.
ضمان سلامتهم وصحتهم.
Nonsense!
هراء!
If Your Highness doubts my words,
إذا شكّ سموكم في كلامي،
have Master Wu open this doll
اطلب من السيد وو أن يفتح هذه الدمية
to see whose name is inside.
لمعرفة اسم الشخص الموجود بالداخل.
Then the truth will be revealed.
ثم ستُكشف الحقيقة.
Fine! Open it then!
حسناً! افتحه إذن!
Master Wu, open it now!
يا سيد وو، افتحه الآن!
Master Wu,
الأستاذ وو،
what are you waiting for?
ماذا تنتظر؟
Must I do it myself?
هل يجب عليّ أن أفعل ذلك بنفسي؟
I dare not. I'll open it now.
لا أجرؤ. سأفتحه الآن.
Master,
يتقن،
whose name is on the slip?
اسم من هو المذكور على الإيصال؟
(Lu Zhen'er, 9th day of the 8th month in the year of Gengyin at the Si hour)
(لو تشن إر، اليوم التاسع من الشهر الثامن في سنة غينغين في ساعة سي)
It's Lu Zhen'er.
إنه لو زينير.
Even if it's a prayer doll,
حتى لو كانت دمية للصلاة،
practicing sorcery within the palace
ممارسة السحر داخل القصر
violates palace rules.
يخالف قواعد القصر.
So punishment cannot be avoided.
لذا لا يمكن تجنب العقاب.
Drag her out and give her 30 strokes of the cane.
اسحبها للخارج واضربها بالعصا ثلاثين ضربة.
- Yes!
- نعم!
Empress Dowager, I...
الإمبراطورة الأرملة، أنا...
Empress Dowager,
الإمبراطورة الأرملة،
I'm innocent!
أنا بريء!
If you act so arbitrarily,
إذا تصرفت بهذه الطريقة التعسفية،
that may sow discontent in the consorts.
قد يؤدي ذلك إلى زرع السخط بين الأزواج.
Who would be discontented?
من الذي سيشعر بالاستياء؟
For a vile consort like you,
لأجل قرينة حقيرة مثلك،
I'm not taking your life here
لن أقتلك هنا
and that's immense mercy.
وهذه رحمة عظيمة.
Thirty strokes seem too lenient.
ثلاثون ضربة تبدو متساهلة للغاية.
She has a sharp tongue.
لديها لسان سليط.
Thirty strokes won't humble her.
لن تُذلها ثلاثون ضربة.
Then make it 50 strokes!
ثم اجعلها 50 ضربة!
Oh!
أوه!
Darn it!
يا إلهي!
(Without power or status,)
(بدون سلطة أو مكانة،)
(I'm at the mercy of others.)
(أنا تحت رحمة الآخرين.)
(No.)
(لا.)
(I can't just do nothing.)
(لا يمكنني أن أبقى مكتوف الأيدي.)
(I must save myself.)
(يجب أن أنقذ نفسي.)
Your Highness, what are you doing?
يا صاحب السمو، ماذا تفعل؟
I did nothing wrong!
لم أفعل أي خطأ!
I won't submit to this!
لن أستسلم لهذا!
Zhen'er, what happened?
زين إير، ماذا حدث؟
It's you.
أنت هو.
Prince Rui.
الأمير روي.
Lu Zhen'er practiced sorcery within the palace.
مارست لو تشن إر السحر داخل القصر.
I punish her according to palace rules.
أعاقبها وفقاً لقواعد القصر.
If you take her away,
إذا أخذتها بعيداً،
do you hold me in any regard?
هل تُكنّ لي أي احترام؟
Following palace rules
اتباعاً لقواعد القصر
or fabricating charges where none existed?
أم تلفيق التهم حيث لا وجود لها؟
Fine.
بخير.
Even if I spared her for this,
حتى لو أبقيتها على قيد الحياة بسبب هذا،
she caused the fight
هي من تسببت في الشجار
between you and His Majesty out of jealousy!
بينك وبين جلالته بدافع الغيرة!
Does such a bewitching consort
هل يوجد مثل هذا الزوج الساحر
not deserve death?
ألا يستحقون الموت؟
You
أنت
envy her.
أغبطها.
I act only to rid Beizhao of her.
أنا أتصرف فقط لأخلص بيزهاو منها.
Xiao Yicheng,
شياو ييتشنغ,
she isn't the innocent girl you imagine.
إنها ليست الفتاة البريئة التي تتخيلها.
Do be fooled.
لا تنخدع.
I know well
أعرف جيداً
who she is.
من هي؟
Don't you worry about it.
لا تقلق بشأن ذلك.
Fine! As you wish.
حسناً! كما تشاء.
She'll be the death of you one day.
ستكون سبب موتك يوماً ما.
Thank you, Your Highness.
شكراً لك يا صاحب السمو.
Zhen'er,
زينير،
Chen Wanyi is vicious and consumed by jealousy.
تشين واني شخص شرير وتسيطر عليه الغيرة.
You must be extra cautious.
يجب عليك توخي الحذر الشديد.
Thanks for the repeated warnings.
شكراً على التحذيرات المتكررة.
I have things to do. See you.
لديّ بعض الأمور لأنجزها. إلى اللقاء.
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك،
Prince Rui rescued Consort Lu.
أنقذ الأمير روي المحظية لو.
Please set your mind at ease.
أرجو أن تطمئن.
So what if he saved her?
وماذا لو أنقذها؟
Her business is none of my concern.
لا شأن لي بشؤونها.
But I fear Empress Dowager
لكنني أخشى الإمبراطورة الأرملة
may harm Consort Lu again.
قد يلحق الضرر بالقرينة لو مرة أخرى.
Not everything in my life is about her.
ليس كل شيء في حياتي يدور حولها.
I'm quite busy myself.
أنا مشغول جداً أيضاً.
Don't bother telling me about her.
لا داعي لإخباري عنها.
Understood, Your Majesty.
مفهوم يا صاحب الجلالة.
Why does
لماذا
the tea taste different from before?
هل طعم الشاي مختلف عن السابق؟
This is Mengding Ganlu tea prepared by Consort Lu.
هذا شاي مينغدينغ غانلو الذي أعدته المحظية لو.
Change it! I don't like it anymore.
غيّروه! لم أعد أحبه.
Yes.
نعم.
Empress Dowager was too cruel.
كانت الإمبراطورة الأرملة قاسية للغاية.
It's bleeding.
إنها تنزف.
She was clearly trying to beat me to death.
كانت تحاول بوضوح أن تضربني حتى الموت.
She couldn't win the late emperor's favor.
لم تستطع كسب رضا الإمبراطور الراحل.
She should examine her own flaws,
ينبغي عليها أن تتفحص عيوبها،
instead of tormenting you.
بدلاً من تعذيبك.
Now look at this.
والآن انظر إلى هذا.
Is she determined to kill you?
هل هي مصممة على قتلك؟
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
I've thought of a way to deal with her.
لقد فكرت في طريقة للتعامل معها.
You're here.
أنت هنا.
I'll take my leave.
سأغادر الآن.
How's your injury?
كيف حال إصابتك؟
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
Only a couple of strikes.
ضربتان فقط.
Prince Rui saved you again today.
أنقذك الأمير روي مرة أخرى اليوم.
He hovers around you constantly.
إنه يحوم حولك باستمرار.
I suspect he has ill intentions toward me.
أظن أن لديه نوايا سيئة تجاهي.
Moreover,
علاوة على ذلك،
today I uncovered an explosive secrete.
اليوم كشفت سراً خطيراً.
Aren't you going to ask?
ألن تسأل؟
Out with it.
قلها بصراحة.
I found
لقد وجدت
Prince Rui and Empress Dowager Chen
الأمير روي والإمبراطورة الأرملة تشين
are having an affair.
يقيمان علاقة غرامية.
Nonsense!
هراء!
I'm not making it up.
أنا لا أختلق هذا الكلام.
I swear on my honor, it's true.
أقسم بشرفي، هذا صحيح.
Even if Prince Rui isn't interested,
حتى لو لم يكن الأمير روي مهتماً،
Empress Dowager Chen absolutely is.
الإمبراطورة الأرملة تشين كذلك بالتأكيد.
Impossible.
مستحيل.
Are you that certain?
هل أنت متأكد إلى هذه الدرجة؟
Though Prince Rui isn't her biological son,
على الرغم من أن الأمير روي ليس ابنها البيولوجي،
their relationship is established.
لقد تم تأسيس علاقتهما.
They're mother and son in name and law.
هما أم وابنها اسماً وقانوناً.
I have no interest in such perverse acts
ليس لدي أي اهتمام بمثل هذه الأفعال المنحرفة
that defile the imperial harem.
التي تدنس الحريم الإمبراطوري.
What does your interest have to do with it?
ما علاقة اهتمامك بالموضوع؟
They're
إنهم
definitely involved.
بالتأكيد متورط.
Ouch!
آخ!
Their relationship isn't your concern.
علاقتهما ليست من شأنك.
Focus on
قم بالتركيز على
why Prince Rui treats you this way.
لماذا يعاملك الأمير روي بهذه الطريقة؟
Who knows the connection between him and the original owner?
من يدري ما هي الصلة بينه وبين المالك الأصلي؟
If only he is banished from the capital.
لو أنه نُفي من العاصمة.
(If I catch those two)
(إذا تمكنت من الإمساك بهذين الاثنين)
(red-handed,)
(متلبساً بالجرم المشهود)
(I can use public opinion)
(يمكنني استخدام الرأي العام)
(to ruin Empress Dowager's reputation)
(لتشويه سمعة الإمبراطورة الأرملة)
(and expel Prince Rui from the capital.)
(وطرد الأمير روي من العاصمة).
(Then she couldn't control me anymore.)
(ثم ​​لم تعد قادرة على السيطرة عليّ.)
(I won't fear acting out of character around Prince Rui.)
(لن أخشى التصرف بشكل غير معتاد أمام الأمير روي.)
(I need to plan this carefully.)
(أحتاج إلى التخطيط لهذا الأمر بعناية.)
You don't want Prince Rui to stay?
ألا تريد أن يبقى الأمير روي؟
Of course not.
بالطبع لا.
Every time I'm near him,
في كل مرة أكون فيها بالقرب منه،
I fear breaking character.
أخشى أن أفقد السيطرة على نفسي.
Don't just sit there.
لا تجلس هناك فقط.
Help me
ساعدني
apply this medicine.
استخدم هذا الدواء.
Lu Zhen'er,
لو زينير،
there are boundaries.
هناك حدود.
How can you undress before me?
كيف يمكنكِ أن تتعرّي أمامي؟
I'm still clothed.
ما زلت أرتدي ملابسي.
Wishful thinking.
مجرد أمنيات.
This spoiled heir
هذا الوريث المدلل
is oddly naive.
إنه ساذج بشكل غريب.
(The 3rd day of the 12th month, Hai hour, Xiao Yicheng will die in the Cold Palace)
(في اليوم الثالث من الشهر الثاني عشر، في ساعة هاي، سيموت شياو ييتشنغ في القصر البارد)
Who put up these posters?
من قام بتعليق هذه الملصقات؟
What's the meaning?
ما المعنى؟
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
Someone wants Prince Rui dead.
هناك من يريد موت الأمير روي.
These posters have spread throughout the palace.
انتشرت هذه الملصقات في جميع أنحاء القصر.
Who'd be this brazen
من ذا الذي يجرؤ على فعل ذلك بوقاحة؟
and openly threaten a prince?
وهل يهددون أميراً علناً؟
Go! Hurry!
انطلق! أسرع!
It has been unsettled lately.
لقد كان الوضع مضطرباً مؤخراً.
Empress Dowager,
الإمبراطورة الأرملة،
rumors have been spreading in the palace recently
انتشرت شائعات في القصر مؤخراً
with posters everywhere saying
مع وجود ملصقات في كل مكان تقول
Prince Rui will die.
سيموت الأمير روي.
Prince Rui?
الأمير روي؟
(The 3rd day of the 12th month, Hai hour, Xiao Yicheng will die in the Cold Palace)
(في اليوم الثالث من الشهر الثاني عشر، في ساعة هاي، سيموت شياو ييتشنغ في القصر البارد)
Now everyone in the palace must've seen this poster.
لا بد أن جميع من في القصر قد شاهدوا هذا الملصق.
Empress Dowager Chen too.
والإمبراطورة الأرملة تشين كذلك.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
تحية طيبة يا صاحب الجلالة.
What are you hiding?
ما الذي تخفيه؟
Nothing. You are mistaken.
لا شيء. أنت مخطئ.
Take it out!
أخرجه!
Hand it over.
سلمه.
(See how he reacts.)
(انظر كيف ستكون ردة فعله.)
What is this?
ما هذا؟
The latest Empress Regnant's Legend?
أحدث أسطورة للإمبراطورة الحاكمة؟
I don't know either.
لا أعرف أيضاً.
It just appeared out of nowhere like that drawing
لقد ظهر فجأة من العدم مثل تلك الرسمة
of the Empress Regnant.
للإمبراطورة الحاكمة.
(The 3rd day of the 12th month, Hai hour, Xiao Yicheng will die in the Cold Palace)
(في اليوم الثالث من الشهر الثاني عشر، في ساعة هاي، سيموت شياو ييتشنغ في القصر البارد)
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
Just surprised that the next victim
أنا مندهش من أن الضحية التالية
is actually Prince Rui.
هو في الواقع الأمير روي.
His dying will be no big deal.
لن يكون موته حدثاً جللاً.
Anyway, it has nothing to do with me.
على أي حال، الأمر لا علاقة لي به.
Only this one?
هذا واحد فقط؟
No others?
لا يوجد غيرهم؟
Just this one.
هذا واحد فقط.
(Empress Regnant's Legend)
(أسطورة الإمبراطورة الحاكمة)
(The 3rd day of the 12th month, Hai hour, Xiao Yicheng will die in the Cold Palace)
(في اليوم الثالث من الشهر الثاني عشر، في ساعة هاي، سيموت شياو ييتشنغ في القصر البارد)
I have never drawn this picture.
لم أرسم هذه الصورة من قبل.
Could it be someone like me
هل يمكن أن يكون شخصًا مثلي؟
standing at a higher dimension
الوقوف في بُعد أعلى
and toying with everyone?
ويتلاعب بالجميع؟
♪Spring comes late after the snow♪
♪يأتي الربيع متأخراً بعد الثلج♪
♪Having endured sorrow and joy♪
♪بعد أن تحملنا الحزن والفرح♪
♪Wandering the streets, the story unfinished♪
♪أتجول في الشوارع، والقصة لم تكتمل♪
♪Turning around, I lost you♪
♪استدرت، ففقدتك♪
♪Separated by the dust of the past♪
♪يفصل بينهما غبار الماضي♪
♪Our reunion veiled by moonlight♪
♪لقاءنا محجوب بضوء القمر♪
♪Grant me indifference or tenderness♪
♪امنحني اللامبالاة أو الحنان♪
♪Crowds push past, brushing shoulders♪
♪تتدافع الحشود، وتتلامس الأكتاف♪
♪Love grows wild within the soul♪
♪ينمو الحبّ بعنفٍ في أعماق الروح♪
♪Longing weaves into a net♪
♪الشوق ينسج في شبكة♪
♪Dare not speak, dare not gaze♪
♪لا تجرؤ على الكلام، لا تجرؤ على النظر♪
♪Yet I crave your glance♪
♪لكنني أتوق إلى نظرتك♪
♪Time, leaving many pasts behind♪
♪الزمن، يترك وراءه الكثير من الماضي♪
♪Desolation follows splendor♪
♪يتبع الخراب البهاء♪
♪Only after seeing enough worldly absurdity♪
♪فقط بعد رؤية ما يكفي من سخافات الدنيا♪
♪Will I kiss your face♪
♪هل سأقبل وجهك؟♪
♪Never forgotten, hope you've been well♪
لن ننساك أبدًا، أتمنى أن تكون بخير
♪Borrowing the first ray of spring light♪
♪استعارة أول شعاع من ضوء الربيع♪
♪Can it bring about for us?♪
♪هل يمكن أن يحقق لنا ذلك؟♪
♪One look back, lasting till the end of time♪
♪نظرة واحدة إلى الوراء، تدوم إلى نهاية الزمان♪
♪Love grows wild within the soul♪
♪ينمو الحبّ بعنفٍ في أعماق الروح♪
♪Longing weaves into a net♪
♪الشوق ينسج في شبكة♪
♪Dare not speak, dare not gaze♪
♪لا تجرؤ على الكلام، لا تجرؤ على النظر♪
♪Yet I crave your glance♪
♪لكنني أتوق إلى نظرتك♪
♪Time, leaving many pasts behind♪
♪الزمن، يترك وراءه الكثير من الماضي♪
♪Desolation follows splendor♪
♪يتبع الخراب البهاء♪
♪Only after seeing enough worldly absurdity♪
♪فقط بعد رؤية ما يكفي من سخافات الدنيا♪
♪Will I kiss your face♪
♪هل سأقبل وجهك؟♪